In the end, all the dreams I've made are
always with you and me
That's right, that's right
If you don't want to be with me, I'll be with you
I can't be with you
It's been a long time since I've had a lot of fun
You and me, you and me
If you love me, if you love me,
I'll be able to meet you in the middle of the night
I don't feel like I'm going to be able to do anything
O, o, o, O, O, wo, o, wo, wo, wo, wo, wo, wo, wo, wo, wo, wo, wo, wo, wo...
When I realized how I had it, it was so close,
that my work and work were on this world,
I wonder where this place is and even if it could only be around the world...
But it's not the only place where we could not make it that I'm not looking away anymore.
A family of adults from the same generation would become much greater,
and together with him, a new interesting place in this world...
The
human voice
What is this?
I came to the other party again.
It's so dirty.
I'm getting it!
Here too! Here too!
Ah! Here too!
You're not gonna be able to do it from the first place!
I see!
You're gonna be able to do it from the first place.
I think this is the time my father came.
Oh, right.
Hey!
You're gonna be able to do it from the first place!
I'm sorry!
Hey!
You're gonna not be able to do it!
This feels bad.
It doesn't make noise a lot.
I don't know how to get by.
My quar illegitimate brother is gonna come!
My quar beneath.
His quar set on foot!
We're gonna go on a mountain,
Oh no!
Come out!
Think about that the other day,
Let's go get some beef!
You know how about it?
Of course you say something.
June 2020
I remember the bones.
bones?
KORRA!
I'm not going to give up on the vegetables!
No, I'm not.
I'm not going to give up on the vegetables.
What?
How much is it?
It's about 3 months.
3 months?
Hurry up and go!
No, no.
I'm going to give up on the noodles.
I want it.
Hey, boss!
I hope you'll make it fast as you just got out,
After having a ride, we'll have a good ride.
Let's go, don't worry!
Yeah, y-yeah!
Hey, you!!!
He died in the third month of his life.
What the hell is this...
No way!
I can't wait, I can't go...
Ah, where did I go?
No, I'm not falling.
Ah, no.
Huh?
I'm going to take a bath.
I turn it off...
...My mother's children are also all gone.
So it's been long since I got out of there, but I can't do anything about it.
...
Then I'll get back to the place...
Ah? Ah! Ah! Ah, but I can't do anything!
Oh, oh, I see. Please be careful.
You're on my knees.
Oh, I don't have any time to eat!
Mipi, you're cute!
You're aegyo, aren't you?
Yeah, I'm aegyo.
I don't know at all!
Mipi-pipi-pipi!
That's right!
You're looking at me!
It's your own side!
Oh, I see...
What about you, Jack?
I can't do anything about this!
Just...
He's fighting again.
He's also fighting again...
He's still fighting again...
Baby...
Is he there?
Not yet.
Why are you doing so?
Do it again!
Dad!
Don't make me to be able to fight you!
He's so sweet!
What's wrong?
Who are you?
Hello.
I'm off.
I've been looking at you for the first time.
I'm a human type.
Yes.
That's me.
Ah!
What are you doing here?
Is it a shopping mall?
Yes.
I heard that a lot of things are happening.
What's wrong?
My vegetables are fresh.
It's a blueberry jam made by Shibuya Chikase.
Well...
This is my favorite vegetable.
Do you want to raise it like that?
I see.
That's good.
If you can do it, you can do it.
It's my father.
Ah, I can't do this.
What's wrong with that?
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
I don't like vegetables.
Oh, no!
I'm sorry.
You're so beautiful.
You don't have to worry.
I'm sorry.
But I can do it.
That's a good idea.
You're welcome.
I love the forest of Soyoukata.
I'm asking you to play the piano.
You're welcome.
I thought you'd feel much more sentimental.
I see.
Do you want to play the piano of Chiri-chan?
Okay!
Go, go!
Hey, hey, let's go, too.
Eh, of course!
See you!
Come again!
Go, go!
Look at this!
Huh?
Oh, my God!
I just felt like my heart was just in front of my eyes.
Is that so?
What are you looking at?
It's weird.
Oh, I see.
But I didn't feel like I was going to die.
I felt like I was going to die by myself.
Me too?
The adults, the children, the animals,
the people who care about everyone's heart
are the people who have the power to die.
Huh?
Look at this.
That's the little boy.
What are you doing?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
You're not going to die if I die!
It's a strange thing.
Huh?
And then,
when the kids of the baby are crying
when they're in a state of panic,
they're in a state of panic
when they're in a state of panic.
The baby of the baby is crying
and the baby of the baby is crying,
the baby of the baby is crying,
Well then, I couldn't go back to the country of Korea, but I was so happy that I could go back to the country of Harun.
Ah, are you happy?
Yes, I want to go to my friends as well, Harun.
I want to go. I want to go to my friends as well, Harun.
Mr. Mangyujin, I'm glad you're here.
Mr. Mangyujin?
Yes.
Is there a place where we went before our Uruel?
If you look at our Uruel, you have to go back to the country.
It must have been a problem.
Wow.
Hey.
Hm.
You're gonna get stuck in this tight.
Huh?
I'm going to head home.
I can't do anything else if you're sick.
Hey!
I thought I was going to die.
I'm so happy.
Huh?
I...
I'm sorry for the dark.
I'm so sorry for the dark.
What?
Oh no!
And again
Ah, I see.
Oh, right.
What's wrong?
Do you know what happened?
Who?
Maybe you're right.
Rain is now getting more and more foggy.
Hmm. Do you know what's left over?
Oh?
Oh, I see.
I see.
I'll come home by myself.
Everyone, please return home without a rain.
It's a tough day.
I'm hungry.
Ah, no.
I'm sorry.
Ah, I'm sorry.
Did you sleep with your sister?
I'm sorry.
I'm going to go get you.
I'm not going to eat you.
Chop chop.
it's okay.
Do it cute!
I didn't know what to do when I said it came.
This is what happens when you stay.
I'm hungry.
You're young now who you're hungry.
I'm here.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Yes, I'm here!
Hurry up and let us cook some rice!
I'm hungry, I'm hungry, I'm hungry!
This is the rice dish!
So, did the rice teacher pull that?
Is it because she's eating?
I think she's just eating.
It's not that wrong!
She said she doesn't like it.
I'll laugh, you see.
That Mr. Hankyoshi is a purple.
I'm not a purple.
Mr. Hankyoshi is a bad person,
but he's a bad guy.
He's a bad guy.
Oh, no, no.
That's the way.
That's right.
I think he can be a purple.
I don't think he can do it.
What?
I'm not a purple.
That's the way he can be a purple.
I...
I can't see it.
Mr. Hankyoshi is a good guy.
If he's a Japanese, it's a problem.
It's a problem.
It's not a problem.
I'm not a bad guy.
That's right.
I think he's a bad guy.
He says he's a purple.
I see.
I think he can be a good guy.
I'm not a bad guy.
I think he can be a purple.
That's the problem.
Baby!
There's water in this place!
Hey!
The water is dangerous!
The water is so dirty, that it's so dirty that it's so dirty that it's so dirty that it's so dirty.
That's why everyone's so careful!
It's so dirty!
Hello?
Mr. Monk.
I'm really good at shopping, but I'm really good at shopping here!
The weather is different from the weather!
I'm going to get a strange smell.
I can't help it.
Ah, her feet!
It feels like she's bleeding too much!
Stop listening to me!
P-P工作.
What?
Crack, crack, crack.
L-L-L-L-L-L-L-L-L-L-L-L-L-L-L-L-L-L-L-L-L!
It's a skull decada, not this.
A skull decada is located in the cave.
An Pose is returned.
...I screamed like that.
...y medicines came from the product.
Come to think of it.
Isurf monday?
No, no, no!
I can't say anything to the other person!
I think I can tell Mr. Hangeu to be like this.
I'll tell you how to do it.
Hello, Mr. Hangeu?
Mr. Hangeu!
Koi-yappa!
Koi-chan, you're a good guy.
I'm not bad at all.
Are you really doing well?
I'm not that bad. I'm always full of stuff.
I'm full of stuff. I'm not eating anything.
I see. I was told that you're a bad guy.
I'm not that bad at all.
Anyway, if you can't eat it, you can't eat it.
If you're hungry, you still have to eat it at home!
Let's go!
Oh!
Oh, no sign.
Kupik!
Hey, hey!
Eh?
Well, Mr. Hankyo...
It's so hard!
Kupik!
Um, Mr. Hankyoji's five-year-old Toka...
Eh?
You didn't answer, right?
Mr. Porano, did you not see Kupik-chan?
Eh?
You didn't?
Eh...
I thought you were calling Porano-san.
I see.
Wait a minute.
Maybe you know the wind.
Kupik!
Eh?
It's so hard.
Kupik!
Mr. Hankyoji's five-year-old Toka...
Mr. Hankyoji!
Kupik!
I can't run away!
I'm here!
Chan, Chan-kun!
This way, this way, this way...
I can't see anything!
Everyone, are you okay?
Everyone, please, me!
I can't see!
What's the matter?
What's wrong?
You were looking for Porano-san, and you lost your way.
What?
Oh, that's right.
It was a very busy day.
Mr. Hangeo.
Good, good, good.
Porano-san.
Could you please be my mother?
What?
Please give me a chance.
Yes.
Where are you?
Me?
There's nothing like that.
Mr. Hangeo.
Good luck with that.
Congratulations, Mr. Hangeo.
Good luck.
I'll be able to eat a little fish from now on.
Good luck, Mr. Hangeo.
I always ask you, but you don't have any fun things.
You're talking about a bad cat, aren't you?
You're talking about a cat.
I'm laughing.
Next time, I'll be talking about a cat.
I'll be looking forward to it.